A. James Delahoussaye collection of Atchafalaya River Basin recordings
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series III: Photographs
  - Photographs from Louella "Duddy" Verrett Louviere
    - Albert 'Putt' Couvillier and Dorothy Bailey, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph412.jpg
    - Albert and Agnes Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph413.jpg
    - Albert Couvillier, Edward Couvillier, Vena Couvillier, and Ella Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph414.jpg
    - Aristle Couvillier's children, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph415.jpg
    - Arthur "Hoss" Couvillier and Edward Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph416.jpg
    - Arthur Sanders (son of Joe), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph417.jpg
    - Bayou Smith, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph418.jpg
    - Bernadette and Anslum, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph419.jpg
    - Bernadette Anslum and unidentified, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph420.jpg
    - Bessie Burns and Nick Burns, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph421.jpg
    - Betty Lou Mayon (daughter of Margaret) and Tootsie Louviere, 1957, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph422.jpg
    - Billy (son of Rose) and unidentified, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph423.jpg
    - Burney Louviere, 1954, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph424.jpg
    - Camille Couvillier (son of Aristle brother of Albert), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph425.jpg
    - Carol Ann Bailey and Elda Mae Verrett, 1952, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph426.jpg
    - Charles Lopez and Nicky Lopez (children of Myrtle Couvillier Lopez), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph427.jpg
    - Charles Lopez, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph428.jpg
    - Charles Lopez, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph429.jpg
    - Charles Lopez, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph430.jpg
    - Charles Lopez, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph431.jpg
    - Charles Lopez, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph432.jpg
    - Charles Lopez, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph433.jpg
    - Charles Lopez, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph434.jpg
    - Clara Gandolf and Anna Mae (mother of Rochelle), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph435.jpg
    - Teacher Claudia Hazen, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph436.jpg
    - Daniel Anslum, Ronald Anslum, Glenn Louviere, and Burney Louviere, 1958, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph437.jpg
    - Della Couvillier (daughter of Joseph "Son" Couvillier), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph438.jpg
    - Della Couvillier (daughter of Joseph "Son" Couvillier), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph439.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey, Louella "Duddy" Verrett, Burney Louviere, and Carlin, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph440.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph441.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey, Floyd Couvillier, and Louella Verrett, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph442.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey and Louella "Duddy" Verrett, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph443.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey, Louella "Duddy" Verrett, and Carlin Lange, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph444.jpg
    - Dot Verrett, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph445.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph446.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph447.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph448.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph449.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph450.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph451.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph452.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph453.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph454.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph455.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph456.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph457.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph458.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph459.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph460.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph461.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph462.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph463.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph464.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph465.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph466.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph467.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph468.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph469.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph470.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph471.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph472.jpg
    - Identities Unknown, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph473.jpg
    - Effes Pamitiere and Letell Guillory, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph474.jpg
    - Elaine Ellen Couvillier at 3 months, 1947, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph475.jpg
    - Elda Mae Anslum, Nellie "Tootsie" C. Verrett, and Elda Mae Verrett, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph476.jpg
    - Elda Mae Anslum, Nellie "Tootsie" Louviere, and Louella "Duddy" Verrett Louviere, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph477.jpg
    - Elda Mae Verrett, 1954, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph478.jpg
    - Elda Mae Verrett and Mary Lee "T-Put" Sauce, 1958, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph479.jpg
    - Elda Mae Verrett, Albert Couvillier and Mrs. Albert "Putt" Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph480.jpg
    - Ella Viola Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph481.jpg
    - Emalina Epha Sanders and Robert Myers Southwell, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph482.jpg
    - Francis Palmetiere, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph483.jpg
    - Gail Louviere, Nellie "Tootsie" Louviere, Arthur Louviere, and Glenn Louviere, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph484.jpg
    - Genevieve Couvillier (daughter of Joseph "Son" Couvillier), 1946-1947, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph485.jpg
    - Glenn Louviere at 4 months, 1958, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph486.jpg
    - Glenn Louviere and Albert Couvillier, February 7, 1959, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph487.jpg
    - Glenn Louviere, Ronald Anslum, Elda Mae Verrett, and Gail Louviere, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph488.jpg
    - Glenn Louviere, Gail Louviere, Burney Louviere, Patsy Louviere, and Louella Louviere, December 1963, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph489.jpg
    - Harry Curtis Lange, 1951, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph490.jpg
    - Hattie Lange Mire, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph491.jpg
    - Hope Sanders (daughter of Henry), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph492.jpg
    - Howard and Myrtle C. Lopez' home in Norco, Louisiana, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph493.jpg
    - Howard Lopez in New Orleans, Louisiana, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph494.jpg
    - Myrtle Lopez and Nicky Lopez (Howard Lopez's sister and husband), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph495.jpg
    - Jesse Victor Higgins, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph496.jpg
    - Jimmy Couvillier (son of Joseph "Son" Couvillier), 1946-1947, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph497.jpg
    - Jimmy Couvillier (son of Joseph "Son" Couvillier), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph498.jpg
    - Joe Sanders (brother of Ella and father of Arthur), 1954, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph499.jpg
    - Carlin Lange, Ira Lee Lange, Gloria Lange, Harry Lange, and Hester Lange, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph500.jpg
    - Leland (son of Ophelia Palmetiere), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph501.jpg
    - Lester Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph502.jpg
    - Linda Darlene Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph503.jpg
    - Linda Faye Lange, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph504.jpg
    - Lorena Lopez, Charles Lopez, and Howard Lopez's sister, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph505.jpg
    - Lorena Lopez and Howard Lopez's sister, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph506.jpg
    - Lorena Lopez, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph507.jpg
    - Lorena Lopez, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph508.jpg
    - Louella "Duddy" Verrett Louviere, Elda Mae Verrett, Nellie Verrett, Eljean Couvillier, and Mary Lee "T-Put" Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph509.jpg
    - Louella "Duddy" Verrett Louviere and Patsy Louviere, December 25, 1962, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph510.jpg
    - Louella "Duddy" Verrett Louviere, 1954, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph511.jpg
    - Louella "Duddy" Verrett Louviere, 1954, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph512.jpg
    - Louella "Duddy" Verrett Louviere and Bonita Couvillier, 1954, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph513.jpg
    - Louella "Duddy" Verrett Louviere and Albert Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph514.jpg
    - Louella "Duddy" Verrett Louviere and Nellie "Tootsie" Louviere, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph515.jpg
    - Margaret Couvillier, Janet Mayon, and Nellie "Tootsie" Louviere, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph516.jpg
    - Milton Sauce, Elda Mae Verrett, Floyd Couvillier, and Edward Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph517.jpg
    - Myrtle Couvillier Lopez, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph518.jpg
    - Myrtle Couvillier, Ella Viola Couvillier, and Vena Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph519.jpg
    - Myrtle Couvillier, Joseph "Son" Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph520.jpg
    - Nellie C. Verrett and Arthur Louviere, 1952, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph521.jpg
    - Nellie Domingue, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph522.jpg
    - Nellie "Tootsie" Louviere and Arthur Louviere, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph523.jpg
    - Nellie "Tootsie" Louviere at a reading lesson, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph524.jpg
    - Lester "Noochie" Couvillier, Elda Mae Verrett, Albert "Putt" Couvillier, and Albert Couvillier, November 8, 1959, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph525.jpg
    - Ophelia Palmetiere, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph526.jpg
    - Ophelia Palmetiere (daughter of Elizabeth Sanders Palmetiere), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph527.jpg
    - Ophelia Palmetiere and Francis Palmetiere (daughters of Elizabeth Sanders Palmetiere), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph528.jpg
    - Patsy Louviere, Marvin Louviere, and Louella "Duddy" Verrett Louviere, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph529.jpg
    - Pete Anslum, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph530.jpg
    - Pete Gandolf, Jr., Pete Gandolf, Sr., Clara Gandolf, Anna Mae Gandolf, and Rochelle Gandolf, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph531.jpg
    - Pete Sanders, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph532.jpg
    - Ricky (son of Elda Fadolia S. and Laury Mayon), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph533.jpg
    - Roy "Bootsie" Millet and Abner Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph534.jpg
    - "Son" Burns, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph535.jpg
    - Soup Dumesnille and Arthur Louviere, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph536.jpg
    - Stephen Persilver, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph537.jpg
    - Stephen Persilver, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph538.jpg
    - The Schoklars (unidentified and Opha Mae), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph539.jpg
    - Thelma Burns, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph540.jpg
    - Tom Reynolds (son of Rose Couvillier), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph541.jpg
    - Tootsie Couvillier Verrettand Floyd Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph542.jpg
    - Nellie "Tootsie" Louviere, February 26, 1960, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph543.jpg
    - Nellie "Tootsie" Louviere, Gail Louviere, Arthur Louviere, Glenn Louviere, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph544.jpg
    - Vina Couvillier and Myrtle Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph545.jpg
    - Viola Lange, Dan Lange, and Artie Buck, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph546.jpg
    - William "Boo" Couvillier and unidentified (son of Joseph), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph547.jpg
    - William 'Boo' Couvillier (son of Joseph "Son" Couvillier), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph548.jpg
  - Photographs from Margaret Couvillier Mayon
    - Unidentified, Delores Mayon, Gloria Mayon, Betty Mayon, Shirley Mayon, and unidentified, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph549.jpg
    - Unidentified and Selena Mayon (mother of Floyd), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph550.jpg
    - Albert Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph551.jpg
    - Albert Couvillier, Jesse Couvillier, and unidentified, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph552.jpg
    - Benny Blankenship and Margaret Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph553.jpg
    - Bernadette Anslum and Emmalina Sanders, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph554.jpg
    - Betty Lou Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph555.jpg
    - Betty Lou Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph556.jpg
    - Betty Mayon, Donald Mayon, Jerry Mayon, Patricia Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph557.jpg
    - Betty Mayon, Donald Mayon, and Patricia Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph558.jpg
    - Betty Mayon, Donald Mayon, and Shirley Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph559.jpg
    - Betty Mayon and Shirley Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph560.jpg
    - Couvillier (child of Abner at 3 months), 1949, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph561.jpg
    - Delores Mayon at age 11, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph562.jpg
    - Delores Mayon at age 15, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph563.jpg
    - Delores Mayon at age 16, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph564.jpg
    - Donald Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph565.jpg
    - Donald Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph566.jpg
    - Duddy Verrettand Burney Louviere, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph567.jpg
    - Ella S. Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph568.jpg
    - Floyd Mayon and Abner Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph569.jpg
    - Floyd Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph570.jpg
    - Glenn and Gail Louviere, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph571.jpg
    - Gloria (daughter of Fedolia), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph572.jpg
    - Janet Mayon and Donald Mayon, September 1957, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph573.jpg
    - Janet Mayon, April 1958, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph574.jpg
    - Janet Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph575.jpg
    - Jerry Mayon at age 1, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph576.jpg
    - Jerry Mayon at age 11, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph577.jpg
    - Jerry Mayon, Danny Mayon, Shirley Mayon, Betty Mayon, Delores Mayon, and Patricia Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph578.jpg
    - Kirt Mayon, Ray Mayon, and Donald Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph579.jpg
    - Kurt Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph580.jpg
    - Margaret and Floyd Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph581.jpg
    - Margaret Couvillier and Lillian Anslum, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph582.jpg
    - Margaret Couvillier, Fedolia Sauce, Abner Couvillier, Violet Couvillier, and Nellie "Tootsie" Louviere, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph583.jpg
    - Margaret Mayon and Edward Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph584.jpg
    - Margaret Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph585.jpg
    - Margaret Mayon and Shirley Mayon at age 3, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph586.jpg
    - Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph587.jpg
    - Milton Bailey and Hester Bailey, September 20, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph588.jpg
    - Myrtle C. Lopez, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph589.jpg
    - Patricia "DeeDee" Mayon at age 1, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph590.jpg
    - Patricia Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph591.jpg
    - Patricia Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph592.jpg
    - Patricia Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph593.jpg
    - Ray Mayon at age 9, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph594.jpg
    - Ray Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph595.jpg
    - Shirley Mayon at age 3, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph596.jpg
    - Shirley Mayon at age 5, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph597.jpg
    - Shirley Mayon at age 7, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph598.jpg
    - Shirley Mayon at age 9, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph599.jpg
    - Shirley Mayon, Delores Mayon, and Ray Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph600.jpg
  - Photographs from Ophelia "Yank" Millet
    - Alberta Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph601.jpg
    - Alfreda Sauce, Elton Sauce and unidentified, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph602.jpg
    - Anna, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph603.jpg
    - Berinda Millet, Ophelia "Yank" Millet, Paget Millet, and Lola Mae Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph604.jpg
    - Blaise Sauce, Ida, Ophelia "Yank" Millet, Agnes Sauce Bailey, Lena Mae Bailey, Robert Sauce, and Cleo Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph605.jpg
    - Roy Charles "Bootsie" Millet, Roy Millet, "Yank" Ophelia Millet, Lola Mae Millet, Berinda Millet, and Paget Millet, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph606.jpg
    - Carol Ann Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph607.jpg
    - Carol Ann Bailey and Lena Mae Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph608.jpg
    - Dalton Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph609.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph610.jpg
    - Floyd, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph611.jpg
    - Jesse Daigle, Jr., and newsclipping, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph612.jpg
    - Lena Mae Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph613.jpg
    - Lena Mae Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph614.jpg
    - Leona "Puna" Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph615.jpg
    - Milton Benoit Bailey, circa 1942, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph616.jpg
    - Milton Benoit Bailey, circa 1942, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph617.jpg
    - Nutt Ackerman and Joe Ackerman, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph618.jpg
    - Robert Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph619.jpg
    - Robert "Tootsie" Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph620.jpg
    - Terence Hypolite Mayon (born 1834), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph621.jpg
  - Photographs from Peggy Rulf Lovell
    - Alfredia (daughter of Francis) and Leroy Guidry, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph622.jpg
    - Florence S. and Alvin Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph623.jpg
    - Florence "Taunt NeeNee" and Alvin Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph624.jpg
    - Francis S. Aucoin and Florence Mayon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph625.jpg
    - Francis Sauce Aucoin, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph626.jpg
    - Lena in tub, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph627.jpg
    - Lena and Ophelia "Yank" Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph628.jpg
    - Ophelia Simoneaux, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph629.jpg
    - Philip Aucoin, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph630.jpg
    - Cheryl, Kay, Harold, Darriel, and Nenia, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph631.jpg
  - Photographs from Ruby Sanders Kelly
    - Frank Pierce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph632.jpg
    - Harold and Darrell, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph633.jpg
    - Harold Joseph and Harold Kelly, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph634.jpg
    - Harold, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph635.jpg